What do you think Why is Russia fighting with
Как ты считаешь Почему Россия воюет с
Ukraine because it wants to get its
Украиной потому что она хохочет вернуть
territories back its own what are these its
территории свои какие это свои
territories eh from Ancient
территории э с Древней
Rus well Ancient Rus are our
Руси так ну Древняя русь - это наши
Kyiv territories Well here you can and
киевские Ну вот здесь можно и
will Hello I see you the imperial
будет здравствуйте я вижу вас имперский
flag behind you are an imperialist
флаг сзади вы имперец
Yes I understand and what are you hiding imperialist imperialist
Да понял а что прячетесь имперец имперец
Well I mean you hide your face
Ну в смысле прячете лицо
hide your face just because well
прячете ну лицо просто потому что ну
because you are an imperialist I understand
потому что имперец я понял обычны
all the usual imperialists are not cowardly imperialist
имперца все такие не трусливы имперец
that I am not cowardly imperialist impe means you
что я не трусливы имперец импе значит
hide your snot Okay Let's chat that
сопли прячете Окей Давайте пообщаемся
's how I understand Are you a Russian nationalist
вот я так понимаю Вы русский националист
or who are you
или кто вы
I am a Russian nationalist
Я русский националист
[music]
[музыка]
Seven yes And what is the glory of Russia can you
Севен да А в чём вот слава России можешь
tell me if your Russia is no longer
сказать если у вас уже Россия не
Russian is that it needs to be gotten rid
русская в том то что её надо избавиться
of
от
immigration what
иммиграции что
immigration Well so besides immigration You have
иммиграции Ну так кроме иммиграции У вас
And in the middle of Russia there are Tatars
же И в середине России есть там татары
Bashkors Chechens who give birth to children And
башкор чеченцы которые рожают по детей А
how many children do you have by the way na
у вас сколько детей кста ня
you are old I am well  pretty well pretty
вам лет мне ну довольно-таки ну довольно
that's how much well 27 27 I wonder how
это сколько ну 27 27 вот интересно как
you Russian nationalist didn't continue the
ты русский националист не продолжил в 27
Russian nation at 27 I continued my
лет русскую нацию я продолжил свою
Russian nation then How many children do you have
русскую нацию то Сколько у тебя детей у
I have one by one or Zero You said
меня один по один или Ноль Ты же говорил
zero zero for those
ноль ноль для тех
who are not in my
кто не в моих
interests I didn't understand I'll
интересах не понял
explain it this way for Russians I have one
объясню так для русских у меня один
child and I continue my nation and my
ребёнок и я продолжаю свою нацию и свой
people so let's say How is it
народ так это допустим Как у вас
now common in
сейчас в
Ukraine for an
Украине
emperor to have one ruler and one nation
импер один правитель и одна нация
I just didn't understand What does it have to do with children
Я просто не понял При чём тут дети у
you have one child or Zero you said
тебя один ребнок или Ноль ты говорил
zero and here you said one Well it depends on what kind of
ноль а тут говорил один Ну смотря какой
child I have What kind of child do you have
у меня ребёнок Какой у тебя ребёнок у
mine is Russian And what did you say zero
меня он русский А что же ты говорил ноль
children zero children This is for you as it is for
детей ноль детей Это для вас как это для
us zero where do you understand
нас ноль де ничего не Поня вы сами
where you are from I am from Israel Israel
откуда будете Я из Израиля Израиль
Yes you want to raise the topic of fascism Now
Да вы хотите Сейчас поднять тему фашизма
no no no yes yes yes yes Absolutely no Yes
нет нет нет да да да да Абсолютно нет Да
why
почему
then one question to you Let's Why are you
тогда один вопрос вам Давайте Почему вы
then now all together
тогда сейчас дружно
everything that you have the wrong
все то что у вас неправильный флаг
Ukrainian flag hanging behind
Украины сзади висит
I get lost in yours  thoughts Let's do it again let's do it
я теряюсь в твоих мыслях Давай ещё раз
I'm from Israel Yes you're from Israel you will
давай я из Израиля Да вы из Израиля вы
support Ukraine That's right Yes what's your
поддержите Украину Всё верно Да тебя как
name Let's get acquainted I'm Dmitry my name is
зовут Давай познакомимся Меня Дмитрий
Aaron
меня Аарон
Aro not Eiron but Aaron Aaron Yes where are you from
Аро не эйрон а Аарон Арон Да вы откуда
Dmitry What city am I from the beautiful city of
Дмитрий Из какого города я прекрасного
Moscow I understand I'm from Ptah pumpkin
города Москва понял Я из Птах тыквы
such a state and city I was in Israel
такого государства и города Я был в Изра
and I'll say So I haven't heard I haven't heard yes
и скажу Так что не слышал не слышал да
But Russians rarely hear look Dmitry
Но русские редко слышат смотрите Дмитрий
here's a
вот вам
question for you What do you think Russia should
вопрос Как вы считаете Россия должна
be for Russians or for all
быть для русских или для всех
nationalities
национальностей
Russia should be those
Россия должна быть те
I'll say for only if people are adequate That is, you as a Russian nationalist are not against Russia being populated by Tajiks And they were the majority there so look I'll tell you So you did
так смотри я тебе скажу Так ты немного
n't quite understand that I'm a Russian nationalist
не понял то что я русский националист
my nation is manifested in the fact that I
моя нация проявляется в том то что я
am like a
являюсь как бы
center
центрим
explain look explain more simply
объясни смотри объяс проще
Russian Russian community heard Probably
русская русская община слышал Наверное
yes heard Yes a Nazi organization Yes and
да слышал Да нацистская организация Да а
why do you call it Well come on first
почему ты её называешь Ну давай сначала
Tell me I'll tell you later
Расскажи я потом скажу
What are the guys doing that is they like me
с Что делают ребята то есть они как и я
support  right
поддерживают правое
movement But for those people who
движение Но для тех людей которые
overdo it
перебарщивать
for prophetic emigrants they overdo it with
для вещих эмигрантов они перебарщивать
their
своими
rights in Russia there is the Constitution of the
правами в России есть Конституции
Russian
Российской
Federation why then if people do not
Федерации почему тогда ели народ не
study
изучает
it super By the way It's interesting with you I
её супер Вот кстати Интересно у вас я
also got acquainted with the Constitution of the
тоже знакомился с Конституцией
Russian Federation you seem to
Российской Федерации у вас там вроде как
have the right to peaceful assembly yes Yes
бы есть право на мирные собрания да Да
everything is correct When was the last time you took
всё верно Когда ты последний раз брал
part in a rally literally 2 days ago
участие в митинге буквально 2 дня назад
and what kind of rally was it a rally we did not have a rally we had it
а что за митинг был
peaceful actions we nominated our
это мирно акции мы выдвигали нашу
organization What does it mean nominated your
организацию Что значит выдвигали вашу
administration and the organization you have
администрацию а организацию ты у тея
where did you nominate it that we are
куда выдвигали вы её выдвигали то что мы
against some laws against which
против каких-то законов против каких вы
laws were you nominated
законов выдвигались
about the latest events in Moscow St. Petersburg
о последних событиях в Москве Питере
Samara what events in Moscow St. Petersburg
Самаре какие события в Москве Питере
Samara and the fact that let's say 2 days ago an
Самаре а то что допустим 2 дня назад
8 year old girl in
девушку 8 лет в
Kazan So what did you advocate for we
Казани Так вы за что выступали мы
advocated that this person be
выступали за то чтобы данного человека
brought to justice and that in
привлекли к у ответственности а что в
Russia justice does not work they do not
России не работает правосудие не
bring people to justice it
привлекают людей к ответственности
works but
работает но
for you it is a little
длях оно немного
different I understand well
другое понял хорошо
but who among the Russian
а вот кто для тебя из русских
nationalists are there for you  such modern
националистов есть таких современным
leaders from Russian nationalists Yes, there are
лидером из русских националистов Да их
very few of them left You probably know
очень мало осталось Ты знаешь наверное
such a group as Russian banner
такую группу как Русский стяг ю
[music]
[музыка]
g rukiy Russian banner he is he is
г рукий Русский стяг он это он там зсво
already singing there zsvo in my opinion Yes no no thank God
уже поёт по-моему Да нет нет слава богу
no that's the
нет вот
landmark group
ориентир группа
rock group that's the
рок-группа
leaders of this group for me are the
вот лидеры этой группы для меня является
founders cool How do you
основоположниками прикольно Как
feel about Misha
относишься к Миша
Mavashi I feel normal our man and
Маваши нормально отношусь наш человек а
to Denis
к Денису
Kapustin Denis Kapustin is now
капустину Денис Капустин сейчас
backing down a little already in the sense of backing
немного сдаёт назад уже в смысле сдаёт
down he is just the coolest Russian
назад он как раз самый крутой русский
nationalist he is the head of the Russian
националист он глава русского
volunteer corps RDK he is backing
добровольческого корпуса РДК он сдаёт
down because he started singing about the sing
назад он потому что начал петь про
head of the RDK Well, the head of the RDK what kind of
спеть начальник РДК Ну глава РДК какой
sing is he he doesn't sing he started creating
он петь он не поёт он начал создавать
tracks for the guys from the Russian corps and
треки для ребят с русского корпуса а
offered them to record
предлагал им записать
tracks they agreed to this
треки они на это согласились
but with one condition that they not be
но с одним условием то чтобы это не
nominated for some big
выдвигались на какие-то большие
platforms like e
платформы типа э
tuba Yandex music and the
туба Яндекс музыки и тому
like
подобное Так
Okay, what do you think Why is Russia at
ладно как ты считаешь Почему Россия
war with Ukraine let's move on to  interesting
воюет с Украиной перейдём к интересному
m you want to touch on this question okay yes
м ты это вопрос хочеш затронуть окей да
and because she wants to return her
а потому что она хочет вернуть свои
territories Her some Her
территории Свои какие-то Свои
territories vision of Rus'
территории зрение Руси
So well ancient Rus' - these are our
Так ну древний Русь - это наши
Kyiv territories Well here it is possible and will
киевские Ну вот здесь можно и
be
будет
that I communicate with you without a mask
что с тобой без маски
Dava
Дава
Okay zhi me about the
Окей жи мне про
relationship of Kievan
отноше Киевской
Rus what relationship do we have where did
Руси какое мы отношение имеем откуда
Kievan Rus come from from Kiev from Kiev And
пошла Киевская Русь из Киева из Киева А
who founded it nobody some
кто основал её никто неки
Hari look then such a
Хари смотри тогда такой
question Yaroslav the Wise
вопрос Ярослав Мудрый
what in questions
что вопро
that the prince of Kiev Yeah that he was the first to
тах что князь Киевский Угу что он первый
create what he created what he created it is
создал что он создал что он создал оно
his from the great publications Well this is not a publication
его из великих изданий Ну это не издание
this is a code a set of laws Russian
это кодекс свод законо русска
truth Russian Truth is not Russian but Rus
правда Русская Правда не русская а
Russian Truth is not Russian there was no
Русь Русская Правда не русская не было
concept of Russian there is Ruska from the word Rus
понятия русска есть Руська от слова Русь
truth of Rus truth of Rus everything is correct So you
правда Руси правда Руси всё верно Так вы
look you yes in the swamps there is a fen
вот смотри вы да на болотах там фену
burn what relationship do you have to our Kyiv
гори какое вы отношение к нашему Киеву
we have Yes and what did we come from there
имеете мы имеем Да а что мы пошли оттуда
Slavs not we Slavs you are not Slavs you
славяне не мы славяне вы не славяне ты
sure of it Yes show me show Look
уверен в этом Да покажи мне покажи
at the time of Yaroslav the Wise
Смотри во времена Ярослава Мудрого
Open any map and look at the
Открой любую карту и посмотри на
territory of the Moscow region or did
территории Московской области или жили
any Slavs live there was no What Look at the
ли какие-то славяне не было Какое Смотри
territory of Ukraine and Belarus lived
э на территории Украины и Беларуси жили
Slavic tribes Polyane Drevlyane Ulichi Tivertsi
славянские племена поляне древляне уличи
Dregovichi White Croats
дреговичи белые хорваты
Krivichi here on the territory of your
кривичи вот на территории вашей
Moscow region name at least one Slavic
Московской области хоть одно Славянское
tribe and you are you now sure that
племя назови а ты ты сейчас уверен в том
yes I am a historian you are a historian Yes 18
что вот да я историк ты историк Да 18
years of practice in a year there will be
лет практики через года будет
dto at the
дто во
time it existed true everything is correct Yes
времена существовало правда всё верно Да
you are saying everything correctly there was a swamp but
ты всё верно говоришь там болото было но
I will tell you one thing My
я тебе скажу одно У меня
parents I have a surname quite
родители у меня фамилия довольно-таки
famous throughout
известная по всей
Russia
России
What Well this should not concern you
Какая Ну это тебе не должно касаться
just the first Four letters say for the sake of
просто первых Четыре буквы скажи ради
interest kr again kr and kri or Kari Kari Kari
интереса кр ещё раз кр и кри или Кари
Yes there is a surname with Kari there is a surname well the
Кари Да нет фамилии на Кари есть фами а
fifth then for the sake of interest just
ну пятую тогда ради интереса просто
what brown
че
brown you can be you
коричневый коричневый ты можешь быть ты
when brown through
когда коричневый через Копится
Brown is accumulating And karich I even  I don't know what kind
коричневый А карич я даже не знаю какое
of Russian surname it is, it's
что за русская фамилия на
Karich, the surname is slightly changed in the
карич фамилия немного изменена в
passport
паспорте
[music]
[музыка]
and so My surname is Krivichi Krivich
а так У меня фамилия кривичи кривич
Krivich Krivich Well, I see that you are Krivich Yes, a
кривич кривич Ну я вижу что ты кривич
little Krivich, a little Buryat, a little Chechen, something like that,
Да немножко кривич немножко буряти
but
там а
you are not yes, yes, I am a
ты нет да да я
Jew And do you know what Adolf did
еврей А вы знаете что делал Адольф
with your nation, I know, yes, he
с вашей нации знаю да
exterminated So listen, tell me, what is
истреблял Так слушай расскажи мне какое
your relation to Kievan Rus, yes,
ты отношение имеешь к Киевской Руси вот
Moscow, look, there was Prince Yaroslav
да Москва смотри был князь Ярослав
the Wise, he made a code of Russian, truth, yes, a
Мудрый сделал кодекс русска правда да
set of laws Yes, U, yes, he had money in the
свод законов Да У да у него деньги были
hryvnia Yes, Ger had a trident like his
гривна Да Гер был тризуб как у его
grandfather Vladimir And what are you,
дедушки Владимира А вот а вы что
Muscovites, What are you doing there, What kind of
москвичи Что вы там делаете Какие вы
Slavs were you, were you
славяне вы были там
NS tribes, some kind of Jurassic tribes,
НС племена какие-то Юрские племена
we lived there, we brought you letters from Kyiv,
жили мы из Киева принесли вам письмена
letters, taught you to read and
буквицы научили вас читать
write, the question is, who is Kirill Fodi
писать вопрос кто такой Кирилл фоди
Bulgarians, enlighteners, enlighten,
Болгары просветители просветите
enlighten, what did they create, they simply
просветите чего создали просто
reformed, they created on its basis the
реформировал создали на его осно
Cyrillic alphabet for writing  on svh yazyka
кириллицу для запи на свх язка
says white ridge as you can hear
говорит бел гряд как слышно
me forgive ra
меня прости ра
[music]
[музыка]
earned Turn off the
заработал Выключи
sound You his sausages
звук Ты его колбас
[laughter]
[смех]
this moment when he was
этот момент когда он
sitting He took off his face lit up
сидел Он снял пере лицо засветил
outweighs And did not hold back the beginning of
перевешивает И не сдержал начал жа
other Russian nationalists I have
других русских националистов У меня для
no likes for you squeaks comments subscribe to
вас нету лайк писка комент подпишись на
my Telegram right now axis VN
мий Telegram прямо зараз ось ВН
apok this is very and very important YouTube takes
апок це дуже и дуже важливо YouTube заня
us through scarg ORV in your ban and very
нас через скарг ОРВ в твый бан и дуже
many videos I do not show people at times I do not
багато видео не показую людям вчасно не
show information about streams so that
показуе информация про стримы тому для
we Mali operational links are
того щоб мы Мали оперативный звязок
written right now and Popik there in
пишиться прямо зараз а Попик там в
telegrams okrim video also tsikava and
телеграми окрим видео ще теж е цикава и
useful information and we are obliged to you
корисна информация и мы повинни з вами
trimati constant operational links
тримати постийний оперативный звязок
independently in that chi show you about this
незалежно в того чи покаже вам про це
YouTube Glory to Ukraine
YouTube Слава украини
letter a
пись а